== Official Website www.kissasia.co  ==
[Connecting to You]
[The 4th Thread] [Personal Distance]
[Redefining Your Relationship by Distance]
Wow.
Doesn't this guy know what fresh food is?
Hey.
Lin Jiakai.
What's wrong?
Could you please
bring me some toilet paper?
Toilet paper? Where is it?
It's on a shelf in the tatami room.
Is it there?
New roommate, hope we get along well.
Hope we get along well.
I won't stay long.
I'll move back in 2 months at most.
Okay.
Please let me finish
using the toilet first.
Sorry, take your time.
-This is really good. Want a bite?
-You, you... this...
Here. Come here.
Don't drop crumbs. Don't.
Get up. Get up.
You really are...
Let me hold this, and you hold this.
Don't drop crumbs. Eat over this.
Be careful.
What are you doing?
Turning on the AC.
Wait. Wait.
Wipe your hands clean.
Is this okay?
Never mind, I'll turn it on for you.
I want the AC on at 24°C.
For an hour.
Only for an hour?
Right, give it to me.
My egg roll.
It's gone.
So many rules.
I tell you, that cop isn't just skeptical;
he's a total neat freak.
Completely different from you.
Go ahead and scold him
if you want, but why go after me?
I can be clean if I want to. I just...
don't want to, okay?
Weren't you going
to sever the thread with him?
And you actually moved in together?
Moved in?
I'm just staying temporarily.
And while I'm at it, see
how to sever the thread.
So have you found out
what the color of the thread
means?
Not yet.
But I just don't get
what this has to do with Dawei and me.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Wait for me a sec.
Go where?
The room is pretty clean.
I thought you were asleep.
There might be mosquitoes in this room,
so I brought you some mosquito repellent.
Thanks. Then...
good night.
Wait.
Did you
say something
about the relationship between us?
Yeah, I...
was just chatting with Chaonan,
saying we used to be cop and suspect,
and now we're suddenly roommates.
It's quite a bizarre connection.
Alright, that's it.
Good night.
Weren't you going to the bathroom?
I'm not in a hurry.
-But holding it is bad for your bladder.
-Don't worry. Don't worry.
Thank you for the mosquito repellent.
Good night.
Not in a hurry?
It's about to burst out.
[Police]
Everyone, your attention, please.
Let me introduce
a new administrative student worker.
Actually, you all know
this student worker.
He is the one who helped
the police solve a case before,
our brave little hero,
Lin Jiakai.
Clap louder, come on.
Come on.
Jiakai has
a special intuition for finding people.
I believe there must be areas
where he can assist us in solving cases.
So I hope you can cooperate seamlessly,
okay?
-Okay.
Dawei.
-Yes.
-You are sitting closest, so it's you.
Me?
Yes.
Show him around the environment
and take good care of him.
Oh, okay.
Nice to meet you.
Could you please help me
take this upstairs?
Thanks.
Perverted College Student,
what are you doing here?
What is going on?
Your Chief asked me before.
I thought you knew,
but you're so surprised.
I didn't know.
And I don't think you
have any professional ability
to work in the police station.
Don't look at me. Keep working.
To copy,
you just put the paper in,
then close the lid.
There's a start button
you can press, and after you press it,
you can select the number of pages
on the side.
Do you understand?
You have a lot of problems.
Just an administrative student worker.
What profession do I need?
And you still talk back.
Our little hero Jiakai.
We just said you could help find people,
and now there is someone for you to find.
People nearby reported
that an elderly person with dementia
was wandering around,
unable to find the way home.
We need to bother you for that...
-Finding someone?
-Yes.
I can do it.
Okay, then I'll leave it to you.
Dawei, I'll trouble you.
This can be considered a profession,
right?
Let's go.
Walk behind me.
Mr. Wu Dawei,
don't be so impatient.
I can really help.
As long as that elder has an ID,
we can find his information
and take him home.
I really don't understand
the point of me bringing you here.
Do you really not
believe in my ability?
I thought you believed me,
so you let me live in your house.
Wu Dawei, you're really
looking for trouble.
Listen carefully.
You absolutely can't let anyone
at the station know
that you're living at my house.
Okay, I won't tell anyone.
And when we go to work,
we absolutely can't arrive
or leave together.
We must stagger our schedules, got it?
Is it necessary to go to such lengths?
Don't you want to be an informant?
An informant's primary responsibility
is secrecy.
Can't you do that?
So am I your informant now?
I'm just teaching you
how to keep a secret,
Perverted College Student.
Dawei!
Your thread just suddenly...
Don't talk to me
about any thread anymore.
I don't understand or see it.
Anyway, the secrecy thing
is settled.
If you can't do it,
I'll have to ask you to move out.
Why are you being like this?
Just listen to me for a second.
Hello.
What's going on?
Why are you panting?
I need to make sure no one sees
me going into Wu Dawei's house.
Doesn't this kind of situation
only happen to female stars
when they're being followed by paparazzi?
What, are you a best actress?
None of your business. Why did you call?
I was going to ask you,
if you were going to treat
a girl to a meal,
do you think it's better to treat her
to Korean BBQ or pasta?
Pasta, then. Why?
Are you going to be a pawn again
and pay for the meal?
You're the pawn. Everyone in your family
is just pawns. Bye-bye!
Weirdo.
He also likes to eat strawberries.
What a coincidence.
You're back.
Yeah.
I cooked dinner for you.
Do you want to eat together?
Is your cooking edible?
Did it take you a long time?
About an hour and a half.
Do you want to try it?
Chaonan had it and said it was better
than restaurant food.
Is it good?
It's alright.
Then you can have this one.
I'll go get mine.
What are you looking at?
Just allergies.
I just happen to have a backache.
Then sit up here.
Why sit on the floor?
What's wrong?
It seems a shiny, oily insect
just passed by.
A cockroach?
You're afraid of cockroaches?
It's flying!
I'll kill it.
It flew away.
There's another one behind you.
Where? Where is it?
Just kidding.
Go away.
Is this how you treat
the person who saved you
from a cockroach?
What if there's a cockroach
in the house next time?
Excuse me.
That's more like it.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Jian.
I'm back.
Long time no see.
-Long time no see, everyone.
-Long time no see.
Cops, your dessert delivery is here.
Glad you have a conscience.
What are you saying?
You still remember to visit old friends.
You're too kind.
Are you really transferring back
to the North District this time?
South District is so chill.
Why make it hard on yourself?
It's not up to me.
Just a routine rotation.
-Hurry up and pick one.
-I've picked one.
You said I had no conscience?
I'll show you what a conscience is.
Senior, where are you
transferring to this time?
Just the police station
in the next district.
I just finished moving my stuff recently.
I think a few days ago,
at the convenience store
near Zhongli High School,
I saw you walk out.
With him.
Wait a minute.
You two went in and out
of the convenience store together?
When did this happen?
Since when are you two so close?
We just...
happened to bump into
each other at the convenience store.
Yeah, I just helped the deadweight
think about
what his next part-time job should be.
You're the deadweight, you...
cockroach-fearing
wimp.
I'm a muscle man.
What do you mean by "wimp"?
Wimp.
Muscle Man eats the cake.
-Muscle Man eats the cake.
-Eat the cake.
Wimp.
Say I'm afraid of cockroaches
one more time, I dare you.
What are you doing?
None of your business.
You bought the bait?
Yeah.
I already put it next to the fridge.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
That's it?
Yeah.
You're not going to laugh at me?
Are you paranoid?
Actually, there's no shame
in being afraid of cockroaches.
Even the bravest people have weaknesses.
Next time a cockroach appears,
I'll protect you.
Is that okay?
No.
Keep speaking, and you'll pay the rent.
By the way,
the guy who delivered the cake
to the police station today—
are you close with him?
I guess so.
He was my senior
back at the police academy.
We worked together briefly in the past.
I owe you one.
Owe me one what?
Anyway, I just owe you one.
I will promise you anything.
That's great.
Ouch!
I'm arresting you under the Stalking
and Harassment Prevention Act!
You're the student worker?
What were you up to?
It's you.
Hi, Jian.
"Hi, Jian"? Why were you sneaking around?
Whatever. Come.
Junior,
come get your student worker.
Why are you two here together?
Ask him. He was following me sneakily.
I thought it was some thug
trying to attack a police officer.
Don't give me this kind of surprise
next time, okay?
By the way, Dawei.
We haven't talked in a while.
Let's meet up some other day.
Sure, text me.
Okay.
What do you want now?
Acting all weird.
Fine.
I wanted to observe the relationship
between you two,
so I secretly followed him.
Him and me?
Why?
Because I saw a blue thread
tied to you a few days ago.
It means the person you're connected to
might bear malice or hostility.
I didn't expect that person
would be Jian.
You suspect he's going to mess with me?
He's my senior and my partner.
Aren't you overthinking it?
I know he's your senior.
But the blue thread is tied to him.
I don't think you understand
how the police force works
or our camaraderie.
That's why I say you're just
an amateur and a deadweight.
There are plenty of
part-time jobs out there.
Why stay at the police station?
Don't be like that.
I... I was just
worried about you.
You don't need to worry about my business.
Here, sweet soup on the house
from the boss.
That's nice.
You know each other well?
I come here often.
I ran into He.
I've asked him out for a meal lately.
Come along next time.
-Sure.
-It's been a while since we hung out.
Yeah, it has.
Let me know the time and place.
Okay.
I noticed something.
Since I transferred to
the precinct next door,
many of our cases
overlap and are connected
to your jurisdiction.
What kind of cooperation do you need?
Just waiting for you to say that.
You know I just transferred,
and I need some performance points.
So I was thinking if,
as for your cases, the parties involved,
and the evidence,
you could split some of that with me.
Senior, we've known each other
for a long time.
You know I don't like
doing things this way.
I know.
Of course, I know.
We've known each other for so long.
But you didn't help me before.
You should at least
make it up to me now, right?
What do you mean?
You're smart.
You definitely know
what I'm talking about.
Councilor, about this bidding project
and the number,
we're agreed, right?
I know.
Didn't we cooperate well last time?
What are you worried about?
Of course, with your help, Councilor,
I'm certainly not worried. Come on.
Let's drink.
Next time, I'll invite you to my office.
I have better liquor there
for you to choose from.
How is it? Is this anonymous tip reliable?
But I think the bribery case involving
this triad boss and the councilor
is a bit complicated.
We should report it
to the commanding officer.
Report what commanding officer?
We should just investigate it ourselves;
then we can make a great contribution.
Senior,
I think the case is not small.
If we don't know what's going on...
I know. I know.
You get off this case for doing well,
but what about me?
Fine then.
If you don't do it,
I'll investigate it myself.
-Don't interfere from now on, understand?
-Senior.
What kind of hero are you trying to be?
The District Prosecutors Office
and the Criminal Investigation Brigade
have been keeping an eye on
that councilor for a long time.
With your messing around,
all the evidence is gone!
Chief, I didn't know
they were already being watched.
I just wanted to properly
handle that anonymous tip-off case.
That's nonsense!
This is the procedure.
Don't you understand?
Is it your first day being a cop?
Get out.
Get out! I don't want
to see you again today!
Go back and wait for
the disciplinary report!
I was worried that it would be dangerous
for you to handle the case alone.
Nonsense.
You're a snitch.
Why are you making it sound so nice?
Get out of my way.
It's fine.
You don't need to rush to answer me.
Think about it.
Auntie, can I have a refill
of this sweet soup?
Of course.
-It's good, right?
-It's good.
Only handsome guys get this.
Only for handsome guys.
You're so sweet‑tongued.
No wonder Dawei keeps coming here.
Thank you.
Jiakai.
What's wrong?
About Jian...
Your strawberry‑print underwear
is so loud.
I'm going to sleep.
I forgot to apologize.
Then I'll get off work first later.
Wait, help me clean up A1
over there first.
Okay.
Thanks.
I didn't ask you
about your left hand or right hand.
I'm asking how things are in your station.
In the station?
Dawei is still number one in performance.
Right, you and Dawei
are in the same police station.
I can't catch up.
Did you come here to eat?
Yes, with Jian and the other guy.
I'll go in first.
Dawei.
Didn't you say before that you owe me one?
Yes.
You'd agree to anything, right?
Speaking of this Wu Dawei,
he really hasn't changed at all.
The few previous times I saw him,
he always had that model-student look.
It really pisses me off to see.
I've brought up the matter of splitting
the case and performance with him,
and I'll see how he answers tonight.
I'm telling you,
if he dares to refuse,
I guarantee that for the cases
he handles in the future,
he won't be able
to get the surveillance footage.
Witnesses and evidence
will both disappear. I'll ruin him.
Then I'd like to see what he will do.
Damn, what are you going to do?
It won't affect me, will it?
So did you know
he was this kind of person?
I didn't know.
The blue thread between you
is produced because of his attitude.
I know what you're going to say.
You don't believe in threads.
I won't say it again.
You're right.
Jian and I did have
some unpleasant history.
But I thought that was in the past.
What kind of unpleasantness?
I stopped him from investigating cases
on his own before.
It was because I wanted
to stop him from making mistakes.
But he seemed to think
I was standing in his way.
Did other colleagues think the same way?
I don't know what others thought.
I haven't told anyone else about this.
I also hope that after hearing this,
you won't be prejudiced against Jian.
So spicy! So spicy! Do you have water?
Oh no, it's getting spicier.
It's getting spicier. What should I do?
Are you copying me?
This is ridiculous.
Not funny. It really hurts.
This is ridiculous. It really hurts, okay?
Who told you to do this to yourself?
I didn't do it on purpose.
So silly.
Let me take a look.
It still hurts.
Blow on it for me.
Hurry up.
Why should I?
It really hurts.
Please, will you?
Please.
Fine. So naggy.
Do you feel any better?
[Peggy Talks Love Psychology]
Two-Minute Love Live Stream.
[Two-Minute Love Live Stream]
It's fleeting, so don't miss it.
Today, I, Ms. Peggy,
have
a special treat for everyone.
Do you see him?
Hello, everyone.
Okay, great.
A very shy young teacher.
So today, with the young teacher here,
what are we going to talk about?
I'll talk about,
well,
personal space.
[Personal Space]
Personal space.
You know what?
The distance between people
and its length
also affect your psychological state.
For example,
a distance of 0 to 15 centimeters—
what is it called?
Intimate distance.
That's right, intimate distance.
Intimate distance
refers to
the distance between relatives,
family, or lovers.
What distance is
between 15 to 45 centimeters?
Personal distance.
Yes, personal distance
is
the distance
between friends
or acquaintances.
What distance is
between 45 to 120 centimeters?
Social.
[Social Distance]
That's right.
It's general social distance.
Distances over 120 centimeters
are what we call
public distance.
Normally, when we
take the MRT
[Take the MRT]
or the elevator,
[Take the Elevator]
we're forced
to be very close to strangers.
Does it feel a bit
uncomfortable?
On the other hand,
if you're with someone
you're flirting with,
and if you can slowly
close the distance to
within 15 centimeters,
[Within 15 Centimeters]
[Intimate Distance]
it means you're a step closer to
success.
[Success]
Is there a comment?
Let me see.
Ms. Peggy, I have a question
about my girlfriend.
She hasn't let me touch her lately.
You could say
the body is very honest.
If your girlfriend
is deliberately
keeping her distance,
don't you know why by now?
Should you prepare for a breakup?
Probably.
He said it.
Bye-bye.
Good luck with your love lives.